<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tsinghua International Blockchain Association on TIBA</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tsinghua International Blockchain Association on TIBA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 14:35:28 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>TIBA AMA Recap #5 - everiToken</title>
      <link>/post/ama-recap-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 14:35:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ama-recap-5/</guid>
      <description>On the 16th of September, TIBA held the fifth event of its #AMA series. We are hosting regular ask me anything sessions with fascinating blockchain projects from China and around the world. We would like to give the international community direct access to these projects and a chance to ask whatever you are interested in.
Scan the QR code below and send &amp;ldquo;AMA&amp;rdquo; to get invited to the TIBA #AMA WeChat group!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event recap | Polkadot in Tsinghua</title>
      <link>/post/2019-09-24-polkadot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 10:02:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019-09-24-polkadot/</guid>
      <description>Under the co-sponsorship of Web3 Foundation, Polkadot and pLIBRA, Polkadot meetup was successfully held on 24 September 2019 at Tsinghua University in Beijing, China. With Dr. Gavin Wood, Dr. Alistair and Hang Yin, founder of pLIBRA acting as honored guests, this event attracted more than 150 Polkadot fans and Tsinghua University students.
Privacy Protection Technology in Web3.0 As the first speaker, Hang Yin, the founder and lead developer of pLIBRA made a keynote speech on Privacy Protection Technology in Web3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event recap | AI &amp; Blockchain</title>
      <link>/post/2019-09-19-ai-blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 09:02:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019-09-19-ai-blockchain/</guid>
      <description>On the 19th of September, TIBA co-hosted an event with TAIS, the AI Association of International Students from Tsinghua. We invited two companies, Cortex Lab and Matrix, to give us a lecture on the connection between Artificial Intelligence and Blockchain. Later on, our guests from the two companies were joined by Professor Wenguang Chen from Tsinghua University and Shize Qin from TokenInsight for a panel discussion.
China is the biggest in the cryptocurrency market right now with over 60% of the hasheries coming from China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TIBA AMA Recap #4 - Saito</title>
      <link>/post/ama-recap-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 15:32:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ama-recap-4/</guid>
      <description>On the 18th of September, TIBA held the fourth event of its #AMA series. We are hosting regular ask me anything sessions with fascinating blockchain projects from China and around the world. We would like to give the international community direct access to these projects and a chance to ask whatever you are interested in.
Scan the QR code below and send &amp;ldquo;AMA&amp;rdquo; to get invited to the TIBA #AMA WeChat group!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI and Blockchain for Everyone!</title>
      <link>/post/2019-ai-blockchain-for-everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 14:03:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019-ai-blockchain-for-everyone/</guid>
      <description>This Wednesday, TIBA held its semester-opening activity on the Tsinghua University campus. Co-hosted with TAIS (the Artificial Intelligence Association of International Students from Tsinghua), the goal of the event was to learn the essential ideas behind Blockchain and AI. We were honored to welcome more than 120 Tsinghua students from countries all around the world.
Blockchain The first talk was a brief introduction to Blockchain by Peter, president of TIBA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TIBA AMA Recap #3 - NEO</title>
      <link>/post/ama-recap-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 22:22:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ama-recap-3/</guid>
      <description>On the 4th of September, TIBA held the third event of its #AMA series. We are going to host regular ask me anything sessions with fascinating blockchain projects from China and around the world. We’d like to give the international community direct access to these projects and a chance to ask whatever you’re interested in. Scan the QR code below to get invited to the TIBA #AMA WeChat group and find out more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TIBA AMA Recap #2 - LibraChina &amp; pLibra</title>
      <link>/post/ama-recap-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 23:45:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ama-recap-2/</guid>
      <description>On the 21st of August, TIBA held the second event of its #AMA series. We are going to host regular ask me anything sessions with fascinating blockchain projects from China and around the world. We’d like to give the international community direct access to these projects and a chance to ask whatever you’re interested in. Scan the QR code below to get invited to the TIBA #AMA WeChat group and find out more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TIBA AMA Recap #1 - Conflux</title>
      <link>/post/ama-recap-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 21:27:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ama-recap-1/</guid>
      <description>On the 7th of August, TIBA kicked off its new AMA series. We are going to host regular ask me anything sessions with fascinating blockchain projects from China and around the world. We&amp;rsquo;d like to give the international community direct access to these projects and a chance to ask whatever you&amp;rsquo;re interested in. Scan the QR code below to get invited to the TIBA #AMA WeChat group and find out more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Reach out if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in hosting an event with us, or you&amp;rsquo;d just like to chat, we&amp;rsquo;d like to hear from you! Shoot us an email at hello@thu-tiba.org or contact us on WeChat!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>